lbox.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy | Mirum

This website is provided by Mirum Inc (“Mirum”). We take very seriously the privacy of our website users and the security of their personal information.

For your convenience, this website contains links to a number of other websites, both inside and outside Mirum. The privacy policies and procedures described here do not apply to those sites; we suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to set out the principles governing our use of personal information that we may obtain about you. By using the websites, or by registering as a user of the services that we provide, you agree to this use. We ask you to read this privacy policy carefully. Any dispute which may arise over privacy will be subject to this policy and the data protection notice (if any) incorporated into this website.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time. We therefore ask you to check it occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this website.

## Personal information collection and use

Mirum will only collect personally identifiable data, such as your name or email address, when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this website. Mirum and the companies we hire will use this information to comply with your request for information or as otherwise disclosed to you when you submit your information.

From time to time, we may refer to that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our services. We may use that information to contact you. We will not otherwise transfer the personally identifiable information you provide at this website to any third party unless otherwise disclosed to you.

## Non-personal information collection and use

In common with many commercial organizations we monitor the use of this website by collecting aggregate information. We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use, the pages you visit or the website which directed you to our site. You cannot be identified from this information and it is used only to assist us in providing an effective service on this website.

## Use of cookies

Cookies are small files which are sent to your web browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. These allow you to carry information across our site without having to re-enter it; it also enables us to analyze web traffic and improve our online services. They cannot be used to identify you. You may set your web browser to notify you of cookie placement requests or to decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contain cookies; those files are stored as part of your internet browser.

## Under 13 year olds

This website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable data from or about any person under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old and wish to ask a question or use this site in any way which requires you to submit your personal information, please get your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.

## Security of your personal data

We have implemented technologies and policies with the objective of protecting your information from unauthorized access and improper use and will update these measures as appropriate as new technologies become available.

## Accuracy of Personal Information

Mirum makes reasonable efforts to keep Personal Information in its possession or control, which is used on an ongoing basis, accurate, complete, current and relevant, based on the most recent information available to us.

It is the responsibility of each individual to ensure that the Personal Information relating to them is accurate, complete and current.

## Access to Personal Information

To request access to Personal Information that we hold about you, we require that you submit your request in writing at the e-mail address or postal address shown below (in How to reach us). You may be able to access your Personal Information and correct, amend or delete it where it is inaccurate, except as follows:

  * The burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question;
  * Providing access to your Personal Information would be likely to reveal Personal Information about others;
  * Disclosing the information would reveal the confidential commercial information of Mirum or its clients.

We will endeavor to provide your requested Personal Information within 30 days of receiving your access request. If we cannot fulfill your request, we will provide you with a written explanation of why we had to deny your access request

## How to reach us

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy and access requests should be directed to James Van Dusen, via email at [James.VanDusen@jwt.com](mailto:james.vandusen@jwt.com) or by mail at JWT, James Van Dusen, 466 Lexington Ave, New York, NY 10017 USA.

Mirum is committed to working with individuals to obtain a fair resolution to any complaints or disputes about privacy and personal information. Mirum's commitment to privacy is demonstrated and documented by our adherence to applicable laws, codes and industry standards and by our adherence to the Safe Harbor Framework. If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with this Privacy Policy and/or the Safe Harbor Framework you should contact James Van Dusen, at the address noted above.
